learnsquared.com 2019-12-25

# Online Privacy Policy | Learn Squared

Learn Squared, Inc., (the “Company”) respects the privacy concerns of the users of its website, [www.learnsquared.com](http://www.learnsquared.com/) (the “Site”). The Company thus provides this privacy statement to explain what information is gathered during a visit to the Site and how such information may be used.

Please also review the Terms of Use at [www.learnsquared.com/terms-conditions](https://www.learnsquared.com/terms-conditions), which also governs use of this Site.

_Your Acceptance of These Terms_ : Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. You accept this Privacy Policy when you sign up for, access, or use our products, services, content, features, technologies or functions offered on our website and all related sites, applications, and services

_Use of Information_ : As a general policy when you visit our Site, we collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes, but is not limited to: data about the pages you access, computer IP address, device ID or unique identifier, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, mobile network information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, referral URL, ad data, and standard web log data and other information.

When you subscribe, complete, or enroll in the Company’s services, mailing lists, downloads, special offers, contests, registration forms, and surveys, you consent and agree to provide us personal information such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address, demographic information such as your age and gender, and personal preference information such as your preferred software and interests.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. The Company may use or disclose personal information, including but not limited to:

  * improve and provide products, services, customer support, and contents of the Site
  * verify your identity and process transactions
  * resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems
  * manage risk, including the detection and prevention of fraudulent activities or policy violations
  * identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with the Company’s rights or property, other users of the Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

We use third parties for secure credit card transaction processing, and we may use and disclose your Personal Information to bill and collect money owed to us. The Company does not store any credit card information it may receive in regard to a specific transaction except as necessary to complete and satisfy its rights and obligations with regard to such transaction.

_Marketing_ : The Company may share information with our business and promotional partners. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties. However, we may use your contact information to send you information about our company and products. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings as provided below in the section labeled “Choice/Opt-Out”.

_Changes in Policy_ : We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make significant changes in the way we treat your personal information, or to the Privacy Policy, we will provide notice to you on the website and/or by some other means, such as email. Please review the changes carefully. Using our website and/or services after a notice of changes has been communicated to you or published on our website, shall constitute consent to the changed terms or practices. If you object to any of the changes to our terms and you no longer wish to use our Services, you should immediately discontinue use of our website and/or services, including closing your account(s).

_Children Age 13 and Under_ : The Company recognizes the special obligation to protect personally identifiable information obtained from children age 13 and under. AS SUCH, IF YOU ARE 13 YEARS OLD OR YOUNGER, THE COMPANY REQUESTS THAT YOU NOT SUBMIT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE SITE OR TO THE COMPANY. If the Company discovers that a child age 13 or younger has signed up on the Site or provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete that child’s identifiable information from our records.

_Use of Cookies_ : Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Site easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Site, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please consult the technical information relevant to your browser for instructions. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Site may not function properly or may be considerably slower.

_Malware/Spyware/Viruses_ : Neither the Company nor the Site knowingly permit the use of malware, spyware, viruses, and/or other similar types of software.

_Links to External Sites_ : The Company is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to the Site. The Company is also not responsible for any information that you might share with such linked websites. You should refer to each website’s respective privacy policy and practices prior to disclosing any information.

_Bulletin Boards and Chat Areas_ : Guests of the Site are solely responsible for the content of messages they post on the Company’s forums, such as chat rooms and bulletin boards. Users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., user name, e-mail address, phone number) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. Please take care when using these features.

_Choice/Opt-Out_ : The Site may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list in order to discontinue any such future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, please follow the specific instructions set forth within the communications you receive from the Company that you no longer wish to receive. If you are unsuccessful in completing the instructions specified in any such communication, please e-mail us at [info@learnsquared.com](mailto:info@learnsquared.com), including a copy of the undesired email attached to the request, and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list.

_Security_ : Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, The Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit via the internet. By transmitting any such information to the Company, you accept that you do so at your own risk.

_Contact Information for Questions, Comments and Complaints_ : If you have any questions, comments or complaints about the Company or about this privacy statement, please contact:

Via email: [info@learnsquared.com](mailto:info@learnsquared.com)

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to the Company such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

Last updated January 22, 2016
